disneyprincessgames.info 2012-03-30

# Disney Princess Games Disney Princess Dress Up Games

Privacy Statement   
_This document was last updated April 9, 2006._

At Disney Princess Games, we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete Disney Princess Games privacy statement.

**Collecting your Personal Information**  
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are asked to register before entering a contest, saving games or posting to the forum. Personal information collected by Disney Princess Games often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

**Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for two primary purposes: 

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once. 
  * To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you. 

Disney Princess Games will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Disney Princess Games or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Disney Princess Games, and, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Disney Princess Games, its Web site, or the public.

**Control of your Personal Information**  
When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, Disney Princess Games will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

**Security of your Personal Information**  
Disney Princess Games strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Disney Princess Games, its subsidiaries, affiliates or agents are located.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

**Changes to this Statement**  
Disney Princess Games will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this Statement, Disney Princess Games will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.
